hello everyone this is E on ey censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is the 25th of March 2024 and
I have Amber with me today I'm excited
to be able to hear a testimony this will
be my first time hearing our sister's
testimony and so I'm looking forward to
hearing what Jesus has done in her life
so thank you Amber for being courageous
and being willing to share what um share
your story with us sure yeah I just want
to bring glory to God and and share what
he has done for me what he has brought
me out of well life before Christ
misery and drug addiction alcoholism so
I'm just going to start from from when I
was uh younger and I I came my mother
and my dad had
divorc and my mother got married again
and there was a lot of um sexual
abuse um from different different other
people not I mean there like one PE one
person in my family and uh the people
that my my mom would leave us
with and
um I I I became an
alcoholic at 15 years
old and um I left home at a very young
age I was out of my house by the time I
was 16 full-blown
alcoholic and then I started messing
with
drugs I have one sister she's my younger
sister we ran the streets and I was gone
all the time and I just didn't come home
one one day so or one night um I mean my
mom mom knew that um I was
drinking and they let us smoke
cigarettes and it was just you know we
just were running the streets my mom was
aware what we were doing um I don't
probably not to the extent of it but she
was
aware so when I had left home of course
my my alcohol alcohol is them just got
worse worse over the
years and there was a point where
I started um the drugs part of it was
not no more
recreational so not only I mean by by
the time I was 20 I was a drug ad drug
addict and an
alcoholic and I did that for many years
um I did get
married and uh he was very abusive and
this I'm just going to tell you how bad
of an alcoholic I was when I left him I
had a I had a broken jaw so I had my w
my jaw wired
shut and they gave me this tube you know
like a
shot like it was a huge shot but without
the needle part it had like a like a
orange tube and it was like six inches
long and what I would do is I would fill
that up with whatever I was
drinking and you know put on the side of
my mouth my my jaws were were wired shut
and I was still drinking I mean I just
looked back on it now I was like so I
mean I could have died on my vomit or
something I know that sounds disgusting
but I me that's how bad of an alcoholic
that I was and a drug addict at that
time so and then I had um I woke up when
I was around 30 years old I had woke up
one morning it was like 3: in the
morning and I I couldn't walk I was
paralyzed and um had to learn how to how
to walk again and and what through
couple surgeries they put me on on pain
pills and that that started my addiction
with opiates for many many years to the
point where the pills weren't H helping
anymore I had to
uh you know I was shooting up dope and I
was a mess I was a mess and I was so
miserable I was in and out of the mental
hospital all the
time I had this anxiety
that was so bad when I would first wake
up in the morning I would be puking
because of this anxiety I don't know I
mean it's hard to explain unless you've
been
there I was just so miserable I tried to
take my life multiple
times and um the last time I did it
you know I I ended up in the
ICU and when I came
home I tried to do it
again I swallowed 90 anti-anxiety pills
that should have killed
me and uh and it didn't I woke
up and
that and that is when I just I was just
so
broken and so
miserable I was just called on the Lord
like please help me I can't do this no
more when I was crawling on the floor I
was so
broken and after all the terrible things
I've
done tell you I've even killed my
children I was was a terrible
person I was involved with a bikers and
all kinds of crazy stuff I've I've been
a horrible
person Amber when you say you killed
your children are you talking about um
abortion yes yes
[Music]
yes
yep and not just one
so matter of fact I was so so messed up
during that time I can't even
remember I can't even remember how
many anyway so that last time I mean I
just I fell to the floor I was like God
please if I
feel was like please help me and I was
just so
broken and
I it felt
like a ton of bricks have just been
lifted lifted off me you know I had um I
call them night terrors and sleep
paralysis and for many many
years and I mean I couldn't even get
pieace of my
sleep and ever
since I slept in peace I don't have
those night those horrible nightmares
and they were very demonic very
demonic and he just he brought me out of
so much my great grandmother she loved
the
Lords so much and she talked about him
all the time she she even took me um to
church a couple times with her you know
if it would have been her way she would
have had us there every Sunday and
Wednesday
but um and and I always believed in God
I even would be set at the bar and I
would talk about God while I was
drinking knew you knew of him but you
didn't know him so then what happened so
how old are you when you decided to
surrender to the
Lord four years ago I was um 49 years
old when that
happened yeah tell us about that what
happened well um like that night I you
know I tried to take my life and I
should have died I should have died I I
had just gotten out of the ICU uh trying
to take my life and came very close to
doing it with and I did um and it was
with taking pills and it wasn't even
half of what I took that that when I
came from the ICU I mean me I should
have died I should have died I should
have died multiple times trying to take
my life and he did not let me die and
I'm so thankful we did because went
straight to hell and I would have
deserved
it
so so yeah when I was 49 years old that
last time last time trying to take my
life and I woke up and I was just so
broken and I was oh I was just I gave up
you know I was like I I can't do it no
more like you you're my you're my only
hope I didn't always believed in him but
I never um talked you know I never
prayed I never called out to him um you
know like so many people do yeah I'm a
Christian but I live the way I want
that's that's what I was you know and I
wasn't you weren you weren't born again
you were you you were you were lost
yeah I was so lost so lost but I always
I always believed in
him I believed um in the father and I
believe that Jesus Christ was his son
and that he died on the cross for
everybody's
sin I believed that but I I I never
prayed I never um you know called out to
him I I I was one of the ones that
um you know I live the way I wanted well
I woke up and I tell you when I first
woke up I was angry okay I was angry
that I woke
up and then I just lost it I was just I
was um I was crying I was on my knees
like crawling on the floor and and I
just started calling out to him like I
cannot do this anymore you I can't do it
I need you okay because what I'm doing
ain't
working you know I I I you know I always
believed in him I never called out to
him and I when I I tell you that when
after I called out to him it was like he
lifted a ton of bricks off of
me it and that night that night I and I
slept in peace like he gave me a piece I
can't um and I I still have it today
it's a piece I can't I don't know I know
it comes from him but it's a piece that
I never um felt before ever so when you
when you called out to him were you
asking forgiveness for your sins oh yes
yes sorry yes I yes I called I called
out to him I was like I can't you know I
I need you I can't do this anymore I was
like please forgive me forgive me how
I've lived and forgive my sins you know
that I and that I
believe I believe in Jesus and I believe
that um you died on the cross for my
sins and I'm just asking for forgiveness
and for you to come into my life and
change me change me wow wow Amber praise
the
Lord pray yeah he is so good I I don't
understand I I don't understand why
people don't believe or don't want to
call on him for salvation because he is
a good he's a good shepherd he's he's
good shepherd I was so miserable so
miserable I you know I longed for death
I longed for death I
did I did and he gave me life
again and I'm just so thankful to him of
what he has done for me in my life he
has changed me I don't even look the
same you know at this time were you at
all in any contact with your sister or
your mom um what was the situation with
your family at that time well
um so I you know I didn't really talked
to my sister my mom we had a we had a
terrible terrible uh
relationship so um the next day well the
first thing I did was started reading
the Bible I had this hunger to to
immediately start um digging into my
King James Bible that my great
grandmother gave
me so I did I was reading the Bible I um
got a hold of my mom and we talk my mom
is now saved praise God she is now um
received the Lord and we have a good
relationship my mom she lives in
Mississippi um so we just you know it's
over the phone but uh we have never I've
never gotten along with my mother well
my sister um was born again a long time
ago um you know she was a church goer
and yeah so yeah my relationship with my
sister I started talking to her I told
her hey you know I came to the Lord and
and we were getting along great have we
had a great
relationship so um
those both those relationships were
mended um almost immediately um like my
mother um we had talked about the past
and we said what we needed to say um to
one
another and and she ended up being born
again now my sister um the sad thing
about it is me and my sister's
relationship was was
wonderful
um um until the Bible changes when I
seen the Bible changes so I had no
longer talk to my sister and I I don't
talk to my mom like I used
to um because they think I'm deceived
they think I'm deceived and Bound for
hell especially my
sister yeah so you know but it they the
relationships were mended you know um
before the whole Bible change changes
when I told him about it started reading
the Bible my King James Bible that my
great grandmother gave me I started
digging in not just reading it but
studying it studying it um and then I um
called my mom and you know our
relationship we said what we needed to
say to one another and mending of our
relationship and then you know saying
with my sister I I called my sister and
told her you know I received the Lord
and that I love her and and our
relationship was mended but and I then I
started going over my sister's house
spending time with her and we were you
know going to church together and doing
things together my everyday
life I was
being called the bible
thumper
um because the friends that I had were
not
um not really Believers so I I didn't
really want to continue you know I
wanted different I wanted to be around
people that love the Lord I wanted to go
to church and you know I wanted
everything different I didn't see things
the way or people the way that I seen
them before but then I felt I need to
tell my the I need to tell them about
Jesus you know because a lot of them
didn't believe me you're like yeah right
you and
Christian okay yeah yeah right you know
it was like that and then when I when I
continued and I would like tell them um
you know tell them about Jesus and and
this and that that was in the Bible you
know that's when they started call me
bible thumper so I just even one of them
was uh mocking God it was my best friend
I had to uh cut it off with her and
I yeah I pray for her um but really I
don't um have many friends I don't I'm
pretty pretty much by myself now I mean
I talk to my mom on occasion I don't
talk to my sister anymore I don't have
any friends even my neighbors think I'm
crazy because I told about the Bible but
um no yeah as far as being around a lot
of people no that's not me um alcoholism
I I stopped drinking
immediately and the drugs I stopped
immediately I did not want anything that
I was doing I didn't
want I seen everything different
everything and I did go through uh
withdrawal you know if if you uh
especially taking pills um yeah you you
will be very very sick but um I went
through it and I didn't care because I
didn't want that in my life anymore I
didn't want to be that kind of a
person so yeah he he literally Changed
Me From the Inside Out From the Inside
Out he changed me and I'm so thankful he
is so merciful if he can save me he can
save anyone if you just if people would
just call out to him and ask for
forgiveness yes I'm I mean I like when I
said I I even look different like my
neighbors I've lived on the same street
for like like 20 years and like two of
my neighbors cuz I even change my hair
color I don't know if that's I just
didn't want anything of that old life
and um yeah a couple neighbors I seen
they didn't even recognize me so he
changed me from the inside out from the
inside out so I um I started talking to
a Christian counselor over the phone and
he'd been a Christian for 30 plus
years then I was told he knew the Bible
and he'd be you know good for me to talk
to so I would notice like um and I can't
remember exactly where it was because
this happened a few different places in
my Bible First I noticed like I would be
missing a verse right like I would tell
him to get his Bible out and I would be
totally missing a verse that he that was
in his King James it was so weird um and
that happened like two or three times
different uh different places in my
Bible and then I asked him why would
there be two men in one bed that doesn't
um it it seems contradicting to me why
there would be too men in one bed you
know why and um I didn't really get an
answer I didn't really get an answer
just kind of like well just because it
is and then I seen one of your videos
and then I knew I mean I knew that what
I had been seeing especially with the
two men in one bed was wrong so you just
validated the feeling I was having that
that was not correct that that that was
not right yeah so immediately like after
I um seen your video I immediately I
like no no no that's I was right there
is something wrong things are changing
but then and I have to tell this because
the enemy really played with my head
with this too you know I went through um
like a too much period of thought I was
losing my mind you know because I was
seeing more things as more things more
changes that were in the Bible that
wouldn't making sense and but he the
enemy was like telling me who who do you
think you are I mean who do you think
you are you just started reading the
Bible you know you just started studying
in it and you know he just do things
like that and and then I was praying you
know I was like God please just show me
um is this wrong yours is right
and he um I woke up one morning while I
was asleep and my ear I was asleep and I
heard the lion will lay with the
lamb and then I popped up out of my bed
and it was on my TV playing an old uh
Bible movie of the story of Jesus life
and it was a lion will lay with a lamb
so God answered my prayer because I was
really having a tough time I mean I
was I went and bought um Bibles for you
know I have like 10 different Bibles I
went and and bought because I was
because my people were telling me no
you're you're being deceived the enemy
is PL with your mind you know he doesn't
want you to go to heaven he he's
deceiving you right now so yeah that's
how I let the enemy get in and start
messing with my head but then when I
prayed and I woke up that morning and
got he answered my prayer
so that's how it happened and you know
now I want to tell everybody that the
Bible's changing and I have neighbors
that won't even talk to me
anymore um yeah it's
crazy well um the um Christian counselor
that that um I was talking
to um I had called him and showed him
some verses and then he seen
it and then there was another person
another lady that um I mean I never
really met her personally but she had
called called my phone she was like
selling something something and then we
started talking and then I told her and
then she seen it and then my phone like
started blocking them you know most of
my life I I was unsaved and and like bad
habits I mean I'm I'm still I have still
have a lot a lot to learn and I forgive
whoever whatever anyone done to me I I I
forgive so I don't let it weigh me down
because when we don't forgive it doesn't
hurt anybody but ourselves and if we
can't forgive we can't be forgiven it's
so um
freeing also to forgive I mean it really
does uh set you free because when I was
reading the Bible it told me you can't
be forgiven if you don't
forgive and and I think that if you
can't
forgive after being saved or there's a
problem Jesus can free you from all of
that
that you own you just need to call out
to him and ask him to forgive you and
come in and change your life and if if
you mean what you say he will he will
change your life and you won't want any
of that stuff or you wouldn't you don't
you wouldn't want to be that person that
you were at all he will take it all from
you he is real he he is so Merc merciful
and full of grace that if you were only
to call out to him and he change your
life growing in Christ every day and um
I have peace I don't um it never went
away like it doesn't matter whatever's
going on in the world because we know a
bunch of craziness is going on we know
what day we're in I I still have peace
that no matter what happens I'm going to
be okay
and it's going to be okay because I have
Christ I feel sorry for those who don't
have him right now I don't see how
they're even but um yeah I have a piece
not I've not had one of those night
terrors sleep paralysis
anything none of it it he took it away
that night and it has never came
back praise God praise the Lord and that
is such a a beautiful testimony and so
one thing that I think of is and I've
shared this before my channel is that
you do not need to be born again to see
the Bible changes right just because you
know see that the Bible now has errors
in it like grammar errors punctuation
errors nonsense versus emotic cons it
doesn't mean you're born again at
all but truly at this point in history
is that unless a person acknowledges and
sees that the Bible is changing they are
now worshiping the Beast because the
changes of scripture are so
heinous and prolific and the changing
literally changing in paper and ink the
gospel story and just the entire there
are Bible changes on every single page
of scripture so praise the Lord that not
only did he open up your eyes and bring
you into salvation which is the greatest
of all gifts but he also opened up your
eyes to see the anomalies and these new
errors now in the Bible so we rejoice
and celebrate this good news in your
life we also praise the Lord for how he
really extended his love and his Mercy
towards you like all those years I feel
like the Lord was suffering with you
because of the pain that you've been
through the
trauma and he waited for you you know he
was a gentleman and he waited for you in
that moment that you called upon the
name of Jesus he rescued and delivered
you and that is so powerful and I know
that your testimony is going to reach
others who might be suffering the same
type of addictions and the same type of
um hurt and pain so wow really rejoicing
in What the Lord Has Done in your life
do you have any U final thoughts there
are even instances uh predicament that I
put myself in um when I was not saved
through the years of you know of My Life
um that I know the Lord was definitely
with me and protecting me um I know that
to be true
so you know Not only was um did he wait
for me to call out him he was Pro he was
protecting me through the years of me
you know growing up and um being around
the people that I was
around and putting myself in those uh
circumstances but um I would just say to
anybody who is suffering today with
addiction
[Music]
or depression of deep
despair or of suicidal thoughts that if
you would just call on the Lord Jesus
for salvation and he will heal you and
he will give you life again a life and a
peace that you never had before he is so
merciful it doesn't matter what you have
done in your life he will forgive you he
will forgive
you so just just call out to him please
while there is still a chance because we
are in the last days we are in the last
hour I believe but yeah I would just
plead with people to please call on him
no matter what you're going through
whether it be addiction or anything just
call out to the Lord for salvation while
he can be
found